<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>403713</bill_id><change_hash>9b0b35ad81115ac0db614881a2907c8c</change_hash><session><session_id>476</session_id><session_name>2012 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB1476/2012</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2012/pdf/history/HB/HB1476.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2012-03-06</status_date><progress><step><date>2012-02-20</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2012-02-20</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2012-03-06</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB1476</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Public assistance benefits; require applicants and recipients to participate in community service programs to qualify.</title><description>An Act To Require Able-bodied Adult Applicants For And Recipients Of Public Benefits In Mississippi To Comply With Mandatory Community Service Program Requirements In Order To Be Eligible; To Provide That Any Such Person Who Does Not Comply Shall Be Ineligible To Receive Public Assistance For A Period Of Time Based On The Services Of Noncompliance; To Provide Procedures And Exceptions For Such Mandatory Community Service Programs To Be Developed By The Mississippi Department Of Human Services; To Provide Criminal Penalties For Willful Violations Of Such Requirements; To Make It Unlawful For Any State Agency To Provide Any Public Benefit In Violation Of Such Requirements; To Amend Sections 43-13-115, 43-17-1, 71-5-511 And 43-33-15, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Specifically Require The Division Of Medicaid, The Department Of Human Services, The Office Of Employment Security And The Mississippi Housing Authorities To Require Applicants Of Public Assistance Programs To Comply With Mandatory Community Service As Required Under This Act; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2012-02-20</date><action>Referred To Public Health and Human Services</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2012-03-06</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>13771</people_id><name>Hank Lott</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>585136</doc_id><date>2012-02-22</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB1476/id/585136</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2012/html/HB/1400-1499/HB1476IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
