<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>400505</bill_id><change_hash>60aab4d9709a933b8a63e2fe47374ae1</change_hash><session><session_id>476</session_id><session_name>2012 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB610/2012</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2012/pdf/history/HB/HB0610.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2012-03-06</status_date><progress><step><date>2012-02-17</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2012-02-17</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2012-03-06</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB610</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Rural Physicians Recruitment and Retention Incentive Grant Program Act; create.</title><description>An Act To Establish The Rural Physician Recruitment And Retention Incentive Grant Program Act For The Purposes Of Creating Financial Incentives To Attract Physicians To Practice Primary Care Medicine In Rural And Medically Underserved Areas In The State Of Mississippi; To Specify The Number Of Years Required To Be Served By A Physician In A Rural Or Medically Underserved Area And The Amount And Schedule Of Payment; To Allow Individuals Who Participated In The Mississippi Rural Physicians Scholarship Program To Be Eligible For Grants; To Provide That The State Department Of Health Shall Administer The Program; To Prescribe The Eligibility Requirements Of Physicians Seeking To Participate In The Program; To Provide That The Grants Shall Be Awarded Subject To Available Funding; To Require Grant Recipients To Enter Into A Written Grant Contract Agreement With The State Department Of Health; To Require The Department To Make Efforts To Establish An Initial Practice Entry Support System For Participants In The Program; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2012-02-17</date><action>Referred To Public Health and Human Services;Appropriations</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2012-03-06</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6517</people_id><name>Cecil Brown</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>580338</doc_id><date>2012-02-17</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB610/id/580338</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2012/html/HB/0600-0699/HB0610IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
