<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>401390</bill_id><change_hash>bb4ea5f3551ef1be77d7accfccf1424d</change_hash><session><session_id>476</session_id><session_name>2012 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB789/2012</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2012/pdf/history/HB/HB0789.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>3</status><status_date>2012-04-18</status_date><progress><step><date>2012-02-20</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2012-02-20</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2012-03-07</date><event>2</event></step><step><date>2012-03-15</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2012-04-18</date><event>3</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB789</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>S</current_body><current_body_id>58</current_body_id><title>Model Business Corporation Act; revise.</title><description>An Act To Amend Section 79-4-1.22, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Clarify Fees Charged And Collected By The Secretary Of State Under The Business Corporation Act; To Amend Section 79-4-1.25, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Revise The Time In Which The Secretary Of State Must Deliver Notice Of A Refusal To File A Document; To Amend Section 79-4-1.29, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise The Fine For Knowingly Signing A False Document; To Amend Section 79-4-1.40, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise Definitions; To Amend Section 79-4-1.41, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Revise Forms Of Notice Considered Sufficient Under The Act; To Amend Section 79-4-4.01, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Revise Requirements Pertaining To Corporation Names; To Amend Section 79-4-4.02, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise Reservation Of A Corporate Name; To Amend Section 79-4-6.20, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Make A Technical Revision To The Provision Dealing With Subscription Of Shares; To Amend Section 79-4-7.04, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Revise The Electronic Transmission Of Consent To An Action; To Amend Section 79-4-7.05, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Provide For Remote Participation; To Create Section 79-4-7.09, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Provide For Electronic Shareholder Meetings; To Amend Section 79-4-7.22, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Allow Electronic Appointment Of A Proxy; To Amend Section 79-4-7.42, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Date Of Delivery Of A Written Demand; To Amend Section 79-4-8.01, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Exercise Of Power By The Board Of Directors; To Amend Section 79-4-8.05, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Expiration Of Terms Of The Board Of Directors; To Amend Section 79-4-8.06, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Staggering Of Terms Of The Board Of Directors; To Amend Section 79-4-8.07, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Resignation Of Directors; To Amend Section 79-4-8.10, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Filling Of Vacancies On The Board Of Directors; To Amend Section 79-4-8.24, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Presumption Of Assent To Corporate Actions; To Create Section 79-4-8.26, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Submission Of A Matter To The Shareholders For A Vote When The Action Is Not Recommended By The Board; To Amend Section 79-4-8.31, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise The Potential Liability Of A Director; To Amend Section 79-4-8.50, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise Definitions; To Amend Section 79-4-8.53, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify Payment Of Expenses Of Litigation; To Amend Section 79-4-8.58, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Restrict Impairment Of Any Existing Right Of Indemnification Or Right To Advances For Expenses By The Subsequent Amendment Of Corporate Articles Or Bylaws; To Amend Section 79-4-8.60, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise Definitions; To Amend Section 79-4-11.01, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise Definitions; To Amend Sections 79-4-11.02, 79-4-11.03 And 79-4-11.04, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Conform To The New Definitions Of &quot;interests,&quot; &quot;eligible Interests&quot; And &quot;membership&quot;; To Amend Section 79-4-11.06, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify Filing Of Articles Of Incorporation; To Amend Section 79-4-11.07, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Conform To The New Definitions Of &quot;interests,&quot; &quot;eligible Interests&quot; And &quot;membership&quot;; To Amend Section 79-4-11.08, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify Abandonment Of A Plan Of Merger Or Share Exchange; To Amend Section 79-4-13.20, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify Certain Notices To Shareholders; To Amend Section 79-4-13.21, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify Assent To An Action To Assert Appraisal Rights; To Amend Section 79-4-13.22, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise The Form Of Notice Of An Action Requiring Appraisal Rights; To Amend Section 79-4-14.21, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Revise Notice Of Dissolution; To Amend Section 79-4-14.22, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Revise Reinstatement; To Amend Section 79-4-15.01, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise The Activities Requiring Certificate; To Amend Section 79-4-15.02, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Transaction Of Business Without Authority; To Amend Section 79-4-15.06, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise The Requirements That Apply To A Corporate Name; To Amend Section 79-4-15.31, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Revise Revocation Of A Foreign Corporation's Certificate Of Authority; To Amend Section 79-4-15.32, Mississippi Code Of 1972, As Amended By House Bill No. 1162, 2012 Regular Session, To Clarify The Continuation In Business Of A Foreign Corporation That Is Reinstated After Administrative Dissolution; To Amend Section 79-4-16.01, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify Required Record Keeping; To Amend Section 79-4-16.02, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify A Shareholder's Right Of Inspection; To Amend Section 79-4-16.06, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify Notice To Shareholders; To Amend Section 79-4-16.20, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Clarify The Annual Financial Statement Requirement; To Create Section 79-4-17.05, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Provide For The Relation Of The Act To The Federal Electronic Signatures Act; To Repeal Section 79-4-16.21, Mississippi Code Of 1972, Dealing With The Reporting Of The Indemnification Of Or Expense Advances To A Director And Certain Share Issues By The Corporation; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2012-02-20</date><action>Referred To Judiciary A</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2012-02-22</date><action>Title Suff Do Pass</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2012-03-07</date><action>Passed</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2012-03-08</date><action>Transmitted To Senate</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2012-03-15</date><action>Referred To Judiciary, Division A</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2012-03-27</date><action>Title Suff Do Pass</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2012-04-09</date><action>Amended</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2012-04-09</date><action>Passed As Amended</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2012-04-10</date><action>Returned For Concurrence</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2012-04-11</date><action>Concurred in Amend From Senate</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2012-04-18</date><action>Enrolled Bill Signed</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2012-04-18</date><action>Enrolled Bill Signed</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2012-04-18</date><action>Due From Governor 04/24/12</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6602</people_id><name>Angela Cockerham</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>7770</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>582142</doc_id><date>2012-02-20</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB789/id/582142</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2012/html/HB/0700-0799/HB0789IN.htm</state_link></text><text><doc_id>603787</doc_id><date>2012-03-08</date><type>Engrossed</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB789/id/603787</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2012/html/HB/0700-0799/HB0789PS.htm</state_link></text><text><doc_id>629098</doc_id><date>2012-04-18</date><type>Enrolled</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB789/id/629098</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2012/html/HB/0700-0799/HB0789SG.htm</state_link></text></texts><votes><vote><roll_call_id>170628</roll_call_id><date>2012-03-07</date><passed>1</passed><desc>House Passed</desc><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/rollcall/HB789/id/170628</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2012/pdf/votes/house/0650013.pdf</state_link></vote><vote><roll_call_id>183530</roll_call_id><date>2012-04-09</date><passed>1</passed><desc>Senate Passed As Amended</desc><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/rollcall/HB789/id/183530</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2012/pdf/votes/senate/0980013.pdf</state_link></vote><vote><roll_call_id>184905</roll_call_id><date>2012-04-11</date><passed>1</passed><desc>House Concurred in Amend From Senate</desc><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/rollcall/HB789/id/184905</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2012/pdf/votes/house/1000004.pdf</state_link></vote></votes></bill></legiscan>
