<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>388450</bill_id><change_hash>04f0418a22bb9f4d0907cfa12156e907</change_hash><session><session_id>476</session_id><session_name>2012 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/SB2309/2012</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2012/pdf/history/SB/SB2309.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2012-03-06</status_date><progress><step><date>2012-02-03</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2012-02-03</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2012-03-06</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>SB2309</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>S</body><body_id>58</body_id><current_body>S</current_body><current_body_id>58</current_body_id><title>Absentee ballots; revise the manner in which absentee ballots are counted.</title><description>An Act To Amend Sections 23-15-637 And 23-15-639, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Provide That The Registrar Shall Keep All Absentee Ballots He Receives By 5:00 P.m. On The Date Preceding The Election And Deliver Them To The Commissioners Of Election, In The Case Of General Elections, And Designated Members Of The County Executive Committee, In The Case Of Primary Elections, By Not Later Than 9:00 P.m. On The Day Of The Election; To Require The Registrar To Prepare A List Of The Persons Who Are Registered To Vote In The Precinct And Who Lawfully Cast An Absentee Ballot And Deliver The List To Each Precinct Before The Polls Open On Election Day; To Require The Election Managers At Each Precinct To Note All Persons On The List Who Appeared In Person And Voted At The Election; To Require The Election Managers To Deliver The List With Notations Of Those Who Voted In Person To The Appropriate Election Officials As Soon As Possible After The Polls Have Closed; To Provide That The Commissioners Of Election Or The Designated County Executive Committee Members Shall Examine The Absentee Ballot Envelopes And Ballots At A Meeting Held For That Purpose Not Later Than 9:00 P.m. On The Day Of The Election; To Require The Rejection Of The Absentee Ballots Of Those Who Voted In Person And For Other Reasons For Which Absentee Ballots May Be Rejected; To Provide That Such Election Officials Shall Count The Absentee Ballots And Add The Votes To The Appropriate Precinct Totals Before The Vote Is Certified; To Amend Sections 23-15-641, 23-15-643 And 23-15-719, Mississippi Code Of 1972, In Conformity Thereto; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2012-02-03</date><action>Referred To Elections</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2012-03-06</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6639</people_id><name>Terry Burton</name><role_id>2</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>562560</doc_id><date>2012-02-03</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/SB2309/id/562560</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2012/html/SB/2300-2399/SB2309IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
