<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>145083</bill_id><change_hash>5236ad1ee014858421394873517883cb</change_hash><session><session_id>44</session_id><session_name>2010 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB120/2010</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2010/pdf/history/HB/HB0120.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2010-02-02</status_date><progress><step><date>2010-01-05</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2010-01-05</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2010-02-02</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB120</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Mental health; create pilot program in Hinds County for single point of entry for persons detained by law enforcement.</title><description>An Act To Establish A Crisis Intervention Team Pilot Program In Hinds County In Which There Will Be A Single Point Of Entry For The Assessment, Triage And Stabilization Of Persons In Need Of Mental Health Services Who Are Detained By Law Enforcement Officers; To Provide That The State Board Of Mental Health Shall Adopt Rules And Regulations Establishing Minimum Standards And Requirements For The Operation Of The Pilot Program And For The Training Of Crisis Intervention Teams; To Provide That The Region 9 Mental Health/mental Retardation Center Shall Contract With The University Of Mississippi Medical Center, St. Dominic Hospital And Central Mississippi Medical Center Under Which One Of The Facilities Will Be Designated As The Single Point Of Entry For Law Enforcement Officers To Bring Persons Who Are In Need Of Mental Health Services; To Provide That The Other Two Facilities Will Assist The Single Point Of Entry Facility In Providing Temporary Treatment Services As Necessary Until The Person Receives Medical Clearance For Transfer; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2010-01-05</date><action>Referred To Public Health and Human Services</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2010-02-02</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6540</people_id><name>Alyce Clarke</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>489280</doc_id><date>2010-03-15</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB120/id/489280</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2010/html/HB/0100-0199/HB0120IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
