<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>146424</bill_id><change_hash>2443da28ec075f2a5c7e2b661ab6cf83</change_hash><session><session_id>44</session_id><session_name>2010 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB1461/2010</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2010/pdf/history/HB/HB1461.xml</state_link><completed>0</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2010-02-11</status_date><progress><step><date>2010-01-18</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2010-01-18</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2010-02-11</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB1461</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Department of Revenue; authorize certain info to be provided to Bd. of Tax Appeals &amp; provide for appeals of IRP registration denials.</title><description>An Act To Amend Section 27-4-3, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Authorize The Board Of Tax Appeals To Obtain, Review, Receive Into Evidence And Otherwise Examine And Consider Applications, Returns, Reports And Any Particulars Set Forth Or Disclosed In Any Application Report Or Return Required On Any Taxes Collected By Reports Received By The Department Of Revenue And Any Other Documents And Information Received, Generated And Maintained By The Department Of Revenue; To Amend Sections 27-3-73, 27-7-83, 27-13-57 And 27-65-81, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Make It Clear That Certain Confidential Information May Be Provided By The Department Of Revenue To The Board Of Tax Appeals; To Amend Section 27-19-123, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Authorize The Department Of Revenue To Exchange Any Information It May Have On Commercial Vehicles With Any Agency Or Department Of The United States Government, The State Of Mississippi Or Any Other State That Is Responsible For Enforcement Of Laws, Rules And Regulations Relating To The Safety Of Commercial Vehicles; To Amend Section 27-19-136, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Provide That Notice Of Assessment Of Motor Vehicle Privilege Taxes And Notice Of Terms Of Payment Of Such Taxes May Be By Regular Mail Instead Of Certified Mail; To Amend Sections 27-77-1, 27-77-11, 27-77-12, 27-77-13 And 27-77-15, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Authorize Appeals To The Board Of Review Of The Department Of Revenue And The Board Of Tax Appeals Of The Denial, Revocation Or Suspension Of The Registration Of A Vehicle Under The Provisions Of The International Registration Plan; To Amend Sections 67-1-71 And 67-1-72, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Make Certain Technical Changes To The Local Option Alcoholic Beverage Control Law; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2010-01-18</date><action>Referred To Ways and Means</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2010-01-27</date><action>Title Suff Do Pass</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>0</importance></step><step><date>2010-02-11</date><action>Died On Calendar</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6493</people_id><name>Percy Watson</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>385664</doc_id><date>2010-03-15</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB1461/id/385664</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2010/html/HB/1400-1499/HB1461IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
