<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>145107</bill_id><change_hash>54b30eb3b50800f72d18a8c9f929b2b9</change_hash><session><session_id>44</session_id><session_name>2010 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB144/2010</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2010/pdf/history/HB/HB0144.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2010-02-02</status_date><progress><step><date>2010-01-05</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2010-01-05</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2010-02-02</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB144</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Broadcasting stations; require certain stations to provide fair opportunity to all candidates when used for campaigns.</title><description>An Act To Require Certain Broadcasting Stations That Receive Public Funds To Afford Equal Opportunity In Use Of Their Stations To All Candidates For Office; To Require Broadcasting Stations To Allow Equal Opportunity And Time For Rebuttals To Positions Taken By Its On-air Announcers Or Commentators During A Certain Period Of Time Before An Election; To Limit The Rate Amount Charged By Broadcasting Stations To Candidates Who Use The Stations In Connection With A Campaign For Public Office; To Provide That A Candidate Can Only Receive Certain Rates If That Candidate Provides Written Certification To The Broadcasting Station; To Require Broadcasting Stations To Maintain A Complete And Verifiable Record Of Requests To Purchase Broadcast Time By Or On Behalf Of Candidates; To Authorize The Secretary Of State To Prescribe Any Rules And Regulations As It May Deem Necessary To Carry Out The Provisions Of This Act; To Exempt From This Act Any Media Editorial That States The Official Position Of The Licensee; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2010-01-05</date><action>Referred To Apportionment and Elections</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2010-02-02</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6510</people_id><name>Brad Mayo</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>3603</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>488312</doc_id><date>2010-03-15</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB144/id/488312</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2010/html/HB/0100-0199/HB0144IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
