<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>477455</bill_id><change_hash>68cf4b7cbc2526e067695f01386e2350</change_hash><session><session_id>1008</session_id><session_name>2013 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB1377/2013</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2013/pdf/history/HB/HB1377.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2013-02-05</status_date><progress><step><date>2013-01-21</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2013-01-21</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2013-02-05</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB1377</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>State Personnel Board; require to create process for state employees to suggest improvement for state agency operations.</title><description>An Act To Require The Executive Director Of The State Personnel Board To Create And Make Available To All State Employees A Process And An Application To Allow State Employees To Suggest Ideas To Improve State Government Operations; To Require The Application To Be Posted On The State Personnel Board's Website; To Direct The Executive Director Of The State Personnel Board To Develop A Method Of Evaluating State Employee Suggestions With The Assistance Of The Executive Director Of Each State Agency; To Require Agency Executive Directors To Respond To Employee Suggestions In A Timely Manner And To Calculate The Projected Savings Of The Suggestion Before Accepting Or Rejecting The Suggestion; To Require The State Auditor To Submit To The Legislature A Report Of A Review Of The Calculated Savings; To Establish The Incentive Of An Honorary Money Award For Employees Whose Suggestion Improves Agency Operations And Realize Savings; To Amend Section 25-9-134, Mississippi Code Of 1972, In Conformity To The Provisions Of This Act; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2013-01-21</date><action>Referred To Appropriations</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2013-02-05</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6523</people_id><name>Bobby Moak</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>422</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>1</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>1</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>711267</doc_id><date>2013-01-29</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB1377/id/711267</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2013/html/HB/1300-1399/HB1377IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
