<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>449561</bill_id><change_hash>427da737cf5e8f98a7ca27597edb7d2b</change_hash><session><session_id>1008</session_id><session_name>2013 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB150/2013</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2013/pdf/history/HB/HB0150.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2013-02-05</status_date><progress><step><date>2013-01-11</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2013-01-11</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2013-02-05</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB150</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Concealed weapon license; courts/mental health treatment facilities notify Dept. of Public Safety of incompetency/commitment orders.</title><description>An Act To Provide That If A Court Adjudicates A Person As Mentally Incompetent Or Orders That A Person Be Committed To A Hospital, Mental Health Treatment Facility Or Other Institution Qualified To Provide Care And Treatment For Persons With Mental Illness, Then The Clerk Of Court Shall Notify The Department Of Public Safety Of Such Order; To Provide That If A Person Voluntarily Commits Himself Or Herself To Such A Hospital, Facility Or Institution, Then The Hospital, Facility Or Institution Shall Notify The Department Of Public Safety; To Provide That The Department May Use The Information Contained In The Notification Solely For Purposes Associated With Issuing, Denying, Suspending Or Revoking Such Person's License, Or Application For A License To Carry A Stun Gun, Concealed Pistol Or Concealed Revolver; To Provide That Records Associated With This Information Are Not Public; To Amend Section 45-9-101, Mississippi Code Of 1972, Require That The Department Maintain An Automated Listing Of Persons Who Are The Subject Of Such Notifications And Review The Listing As Necessary; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2013-01-11</date><action>Referred To Public Health and Human Services;Judiciary B</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2013-02-05</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6566</people_id><name>Andy Gipson</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>9032</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>1</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>1</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>681665</doc_id><date>2013-01-11</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB150/id/681665</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2013/html/HB/0100-0199/HB0150IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
