<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>451732</bill_id><change_hash>6b8360d4b91ca6401df774f64304cca3</change_hash><session><session_id>1008</session_id><session_name>2013 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB351/2013</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2013/pdf/history/HB/HB0351.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2013-02-05</status_date><progress><step><date>2013-01-14</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2013-01-14</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2013-02-05</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB351</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Medicaid; provide for a database of electronic medical records of Medicaid recipients, with access by Medicaid providers.</title><description>An Act To Direct The Division Of Medicaid To Contract With An Entity To Develop, Maintain And Operate A Database Of Electronic Medical Records Of Medicaid Recipients, Which May Be Accessed By Medicaid Providers To Obtain The Medical Records Of Medicaid Recipients To Whom They Are Providing Services; To Provide That The Purpose Of The Database Is To Allow Health Care Providers To Be Able To Coordinate Services To Medicaid Recipients With Those Provided By Other Health Care Providers In A Manner To Optimize The Quality, Efficiency And Safety Of The Health Care Received By Medicaid Recipients; To Require That The Database Shall Be Designed To Limit Access To The Medical Records Of Any Particular Individual Only To Those Medicaid Providers Who Provide Services To That Individual; To Direct The Division To Adopt Rules And Regulations To Provide That Medicaid Providers Shall Transfer To The Electronic Medical Records Database The Medical Records Information For The Medicaid Recipients To Whom They Provide Services; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2013-01-14</date><action>Referred To Medicaid;Appropriations</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2013-02-05</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6524</people_id><name>Omeria Scott</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>1</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>1</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>684992</doc_id><date>2013-01-14</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB351/id/684992</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2013/html/HB/0300-0399/HB0351IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
