<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>583401</bill_id><change_hash>deb0a2082fa2caf8ff3fa5d69351e217</change_hash><session><session_id>1083</session_id><session_name>2014 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB150/2014</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2014/pdf/history/HB/HB0150.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2014-02-04</status_date><progress><step><date>2014-01-13</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2014-01-13</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2014-02-04</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB150</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>School districts; require certain policies if accredited at three lowest levels and alternative curriculum.</title><description>An Act To Require School Districts Accredited At One Of The Three Lowest Accreditation Levels, As Defined By The State Board Of Education, To Adopt Certain Policies And Procedures Regarding Daily Curriculum, Weekly Homework Assignments, Parental Involvement, Dress Codes, School Holidays, Parent-teacher Conferences And A School Syllabus; To Require Alternative Schools In Those Districts To Adhere To The Same Policies And Procedures; To Require Local School Districts To Implement A Video Streaming Program In Conjunction With The United States Department Of Labor To Aid In The Development Of An Alternative Career-track Curriculum Based Upon Occupational Projections In The State And Country For The Next Five Years; To Require School Districts To Assist Students In Accessing Information From The Department Of Labor Which Will Enable The Students To Make Career Choices; To Require A School District's Alternative Career-track Curriculum To Satisfy Its Graduation Requirements And Lead To The Awarding Of A Standard High School Diploma; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2014-01-13</date><action>Referred To Education;Appropriations</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2014-02-04</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6524</people_id><name>Omeria Scott</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>1</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>1</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>912164</doc_id><date>2014-01-13</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB150/id/912164</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2014/html/HB/0100-0199/HB0150IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
