<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>598326</bill_id><change_hash>7e32b62723d7b56edc0a1defe208c1e9</change_hash><session><session_id>1083</session_id><session_name>2014 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB369/2014</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2014/pdf/history/HB/HB0369.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2014-02-04</status_date><progress><step><date>2014-01-20</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2014-01-20</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2014-02-04</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB369</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>End-of-course subject area tests; prohibit mandatory passing scores as requirement for graduation.</title><description>An Act To Prohibit The State Board Of Education From Requiring Students To Achieve A Passing Score On End-of-course Tests Administered Under The Subject Area Testing Program As A Requirement For Graduation; To Amend Section 37-16-7, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Prohibit Local School Districts From Using The End-of-course Tests To Determine If Students Have Mastered Minimum Academic Skills Required For Graduation; To Amend Section 37-15-38, Mississippi Code Of 1972, In Conformity To The Provisions Of This Act; To Bring Forward Section 37-3-49, Mississippi Code Of 1972, Which Requires The State Department Of Education To Provide An Instructional Program For All Courses In The End-of-course Testing Program, For Purposes Of Possible Amendment; To Bring Forward Section 37-16-17, Mississippi Code Of 1972, Which Requires School Districts To Offer A Career Track Program, For Purposes Of Possible Amendment; To Bring Forward Section 37-35-3, Mississippi Code Of 1972, Which Authorizes School Districts To Establish A General Educational Development (ged) Option Program, For Purposes Of Possible Amendment; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2014-01-20</date><action>Referred To Education</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2014-02-04</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber>H</chamber><chamber_id>57</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>13808</people_id><name>Deborah Butler Dixon</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>1</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>1</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>929190</doc_id><date>2014-01-20</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB369/id/929190</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2014/html/HB/0300-0399/HB0369IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
