<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>598380</bill_id><change_hash>06d7dd29d464f1ec6ceb277fe8e64423</change_hash><session><session_id>1083</session_id><session_name>2014 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/SB2422/2014</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2014/pdf/history/SB/SB2422.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2014-02-04</status_date><progress><step><date>2014-01-20</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2014-01-20</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2014-02-04</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>SB2422</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>S</body><body_id>58</body_id><current_body>S</current_body><current_body_id>58</current_body_id><title>Public School Districts of Innovation; authorize State Board of Education to approve creation of in local school districts.</title><description>An Act To Authorize The State Board Of Education To Approve The Creation Of Public School Districts Of Innovation; To Define Certain Terms Related To &quot;public School Districts Of Innovation&quot;; To Provide That The Number Of Districts Of Innovation Approved Shall Not Exceed Five Districts Per Year; To Limit The Initial Approval And Subsequent Renewals Of Districts Of Innovation To Five-year Periods; To Direct The Board To Promulgate Administrative Rules And Regulations To Prescribe The Conditions And Procedures To Be Used By Local School Boards To Be Approved As A District Of Innovation; To Specify The Criteria To Be Addressed By The Administrative Regulations; To Prescribe The Requirements For A District To Be A District Of Innovation Applicant; To Prescribe The Statutory Requirements With Which Schools Of Innovation Within Districts Of Innovation Must Comply; To Identify Areas In Which Districts Of Innovation May Request Approval Of Practices That Are Different Than Current Statutory Requirements; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2014-01-20</date><action>Referred To Education</action><chamber>S</chamber><chamber_id>58</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2014-02-04</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber>S</chamber><chamber_id>58</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6636</people_id><name>Gray Tollison</name><role_id>2</role_id><ftm_id>2248</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>1</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>1</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>929239</doc_id><date>2014-01-20</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/SB2422/id/929239</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2014/html/SB/2400-2499/SB2422IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
