<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>599983</bill_id><change_hash>145373e216a5576d4c7d6ba1a1785057</change_hash><session><session_id>1083</session_id><session_name>2014 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/SB2589/2014</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2014/pdf/history/SB/SB2589.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2014-02-04</status_date><progress><step><date>2014-01-20</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2014-01-20</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2014-02-04</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>SB2589</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>S</body><body_id>58</body_id><current_body>S</current_body><current_body_id>58</current_body_id><title>Alcoholic beverages; authorize package retailers to sample product and hold tasting/sampling events.</title><description>An Act To Amend Section 67-1-51, Mississippi Code Of 1972, Relating To The Local Option Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, To Provide That A Package Retailer's Permit Shall Authorize The Holder To Sample New Product Furnished By A Manufacturer's Representative Or His Employees At The Permitted Place Of Business; To Provide That Such Samples May Not Be Provided To Customers At The Permitted Place Of Business; To Provide That A Package Retailer's Permit Shall Authorize Tasting Or Sampling Events To Be Conducted At The Package Retailer's Permitted Place Of Business During Which Tastes Or Samples Of Alcoholic Beverages May Be Offered Or Served To Consumers At No Cost; To Limit The Duration Of Tasting Or Sampling Events And The Amount Of Alcoholic Beverage That May Be Served To Any One Person At Such Events; To Provide That The Product Tasted Or Sampled At Such Events Must Be Product That Is In The Inventory Of The Package Retailer Conducting The Event; To Provide That A Package Retailer May Conduct Not More Than Twelve Events During A Calendar Year; To Amend Section 67-1-75, Mississippi Code Of 1972, In Conformity Thereto; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2014-01-20</date><action>Referred To Tourism</action><chamber>S</chamber><chamber_id>58</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2014-02-04</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber>S</chamber><chamber_id>58</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6646</people_id><name>Lydia Chassaniol</name><role_id>2</role_id><ftm_id>378</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>1</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>1</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>930929</doc_id><date>2014-01-21</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/SB2589/id/930929</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2014/html/SB/2500-2599/SB2589IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
