<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>224499</bill_id><change_hash>7cda8a7e409036e01ab34f51166fddff</change_hash><session><session_id>87</session_id><session_name>2011 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB526/2011</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2011/pdf/history/HB/HB0526.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2011-02-01</status_date><progress><step><date>2011-01-10</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2011-01-10</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2011-02-01</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB526</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>&quot;Mississippi Agricultural Renewable Energy Development Act of 2011&quot;; create.</title><description>An Act To Create The &quot;mississippi Agricultural Renewable Energy Development Act Of 2011&quot;; To Provide Certain Definitions; To Provide Certain Requirements Of Electricity Providers That Provide Net Metering; To Provide That Any Excess Kilo-watt Hours (kwh) Credits Earned By Customer-generators Are To Be Applied To Subsequent Billing Periods For Offsetting Purposes; To Provide If Customer-generators Cease Metering Services, Then The Electricity Providers Are Not Required To Provide Compensation For Any Outstanding Excess Kwh; To Require That Electricity Providers Offer Electric Service At Nondiscriminatory Rates; To Require Electricity Providers To Submit An Annual Net Metering Report To The Public Service Commission That Contains Total Customer-generator Facilities, Total Rated Generating Capacity Of Such Facilities And The Total Number Of Kwh Received From Net Metered Customer-generators; To Authorize Customer-generators To Participate In Meter Aggregation; To Provide The Commission, After Opportunity For Public Comment, Shall Establish Appropriate Rates, Terms And Conditions For Net Metering Contracts; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2011-01-10</date><action>Referred To Agriculture;Public Utilities</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2011-02-01</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6542</people_id><name>Mark Baker</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>0</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>237573</doc_id><date>2011-01-10</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB526/id/237573</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2011/html/HB/0500-0599/HB0526IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
