<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>227896</bill_id><change_hash>258d1f7bf06e719b88bbe8ab0fe039c5</change_hash><session><session_id>87</session_id><session_name>2011 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB797/2011</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2011/pdf/history/HB/HB0797.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2011-02-01</status_date><progress><step><date>2011-01-14</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2011-01-14</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2011-02-01</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB797</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Burn Center; repeal requirement for UMMC to establish and provide for reimbursement for certain other burn centers.</title><description>An Act To Repeal Section 37-115-45, Mississippi Code Of 1972, Which Directs The University Of Mississippi Medical Center To Establish The Mississippi Burn Center As A Separate Unit At The Medical Center For The Treatment Of Burn Victims; To Amend Section 41-59-5, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Provide That The Joseph M. Still Burn Centers And The Mississippi Burn Center At Crossgates River Oaks Hospital Shall Receive A Reasonable Amount Of Reimbursement From The State Department Of Health For The Cost Of Providing Burn Care Services To Mississippi Residents Whose Treatment Is Uncompensated; To Provide That The Plan Developed By The State Board Of Health For The Delivery Of Services To Mississippi Burn Victims Shall Include Systems By Which Burn Patients Will Be Assigned Or Transferred To Any Certified Burn Center Designated By The Department, And Procedures For Allocating Funds Appropriated From The Mississippi Burn Care Fund To Certified Burn Centers Designated By The Department That Provide Services To Mississippi Burn Victims; To Amend Sections 7-9-70, 21-19-58, 27-19-44.3, 27-39-331 And 27-39-332, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Conform To The Preceding Provisions; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2011-01-14</date><action>Referred To Public Health and Human Services;Appropriations</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2011-02-01</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6504</people_id><name>Stephen Holland</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>15093</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>238838</doc_id><date>2011-01-14</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB797/id/238838</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2011/html/HB/0700-0799/HB0797IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
