<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legiscan><status></status><bill><bill_id>229195</bill_id><change_hash>691404d5273ee57ff7a5c8a88879596d</change_hash><session><session_id>87</session_id><session_name>2011 Regular Session</session_name></session><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/bill/HB837/2011</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/2011/pdf/history/HB/HB0837.xml</state_link><completed>1</completed><status>6</status><status_date>2011-02-01</status_date><progress><step><date>2011-01-17</date><event>1</event></step><step><date>2011-01-17</date><event>9</event></step><step><date>2011-02-01</date><event>6</event></step></progress><state>MS</state><state_id>24</state_id><bill_number>HB837</bill_number><bill_type>B</bill_type><body>H</body><body_id>57</body_id><current_body>H</current_body><current_body_id>57</current_body_id><title>Retirement; participants in optional retirement program may become PERS members and purchase credit for previous service.</title><description>An Act To Amend Section 25-11-413, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Provide A Three-month Period During Which Any Participant In The Optional Retirement Program (orp) For Employees Of State Institutions Of Higher Learning May Cease Participating In The Orp And Become A Member Of The Public Employees' Retirement System (pers); To Provide That Any Person Who Becomes A Member Of Pers Under This Provision Shall Retain All Benefits Earned Under The Orp Up To The Date That The Person Became A Member Of Pers, But Shall Not Make Any Further Contributions To The Orp; To Amend Section 25-11-109, Mississippi Code Of 1972, To Provide That Certain Participants In The Orp Who Cease Participation In The Orp And Become A Member Of Pers Shall Be Entitled To Receive A Maximum Of Ten Years Creditable Service For Service Rendered As A Teaching Or Administrative Faculty Employee Of A State Institution Of Higher Learning In Mississippi While Participating In The Orp; To Require The Member To Pay Into Pers The Actuarial Cost As Determined By The Actuary For Each Year, Or Portion Thereof, Of That Service; And For Related Purposes.</description><committee/><history><step><date>2011-01-17</date><action>Referred To Appropriations</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step><step><date>2011-02-01</date><action>Died In Committee</action><chamber></chamber><chamber_id>0</chamber_id><importance>1</importance></step></history><sponsors><sponsor><people_id>6581</people_id><name>Blaine Eaton</name><role_id>1</role_id><ftm_id>2238</ftm_id><sponsor_type_id>0</sponsor_type_id><sponsor_order>0</sponsor_order></sponsor></sponsors><texts><text><doc_id>238632</doc_id><date>2011-01-17</date><type>Introduced</type><mime>text/html</mime><url>http://legiscan.com/MS/text/HB837/id/238632</url><state_link>http://billstatus.ls.state.ms.us/documents/2011/html/HB/0800-0899/HB0837IN.htm</state_link></text></texts></bill></legiscan>
